[unsettling music]
[NASA Launch Announcer]
Ten, nine, eight,
seven, six, five,
four, three, two, one.
[blast]
We have ignition,
we have a liftoff.
[unsettling music]
[NASA Flight Announcer]
...program is in on time,
and the response is normal.
[unsettling music]
[beeping]
[Chuck Berry's
Johnny B. Goodeplaying]
♪ Go, Johnny, go, go ♪
♪ Johnny B. Goode ♪
[overwhelming music]
♪ Deep down in Louisiana
close to New Orleans ♪
♪ Way back up in the woods
among the evergreens ♪
[overwhelming music]
[gunfire]
[rumbling, explosions]
[action music]
[gunfire]
[shouting]
Move! Move!
Hold on!
Roger that.
Full sweep.
Go left.
Careful.
[action music]
[shouting]
Here they come!
Fucking idiot.
[shouting]
[grunts]
[screams]
You're welcome.
[gunshots]
They're right.
Clear left.
All clear.
Stairs on me, boys.
[loud blast]
[glass shattering]
Donnie, which way?
This should be Fordosa.
Left takes
us to the Aziziyah District,
towards the friendlies.
[gunfire]
- Move it.
- Move.
[shouting]
[gunfire, blasts]
[shouting,
frantic chatter]
Rhodie! We can't stay here!
[gunfire]
Way out on me!
Move!
Move it!
[shouting]
- Cover!
- The fuck!?
Come on, fuckers!
[gunfire]
Jax, move! Jax!
[shouting]
Move, move!
[gunfire]
Let's move!
[shouting]
I got you, man.
I got you.
[gunfire]
[action music]
I got it, I got it.
[shouting]
[action music]
Jax!
Let's go!
[gunfire]
He's gone!
[shouting]
Pull yourselves up!
Negative, negative!
They're on top of us!
[gunfire]
[shouting]
Where's the fucking QRF!?
Jammed up!
Five minutes out!
This shit is over in two!
[shouting]
[gunfire]
[boom]
- Go in there and light us up!
- Are you crazy?!
I said go in there!
This is Bravo One Zulu
requesting an ordnance drop.
Our GRID is 07238947.
Yes, I know
it's our fucking position!
Send it! Danger close!
Drop the motherfucker!
[shouting]
[gunfire]
[boom]
[dramatic, sinister music]
[blast]
[zapping, sparking]
[static]
[blast]
[silence]
[screams]
[cacophony of sound]
[low rumbling]
[unsettling music]
[hissing]
[intensifying music]
[muffled struggling]
[groans]
[thudding]
[coughing, retching]
Come on.
Are you good?
Solid.
You?
[coughing, retching]
Fuck! Fuck me!
[Jax] I know, right?
[coughing, retching]
This is tier one bullshit, man.
I just wanna know who to kill.
'Cause someone's definitely
getting blood for this shit.
Jax, what the fuck
is this shit, man?
Stasis resin residue.
It should dissolve quickly.
How do you know that?
I don't know, I just do.
Kelly.
Oh, Jesus, fuck, man!
Oh, Jesus, dude.
What's happening here, boys?
Fucking...
- You calm down.
- Calm down?
I just woke up in a fishbowl
in this goofy house of horrors.
And you want me to calm down?
Yeah, shut it!
Where the hell are we?
Black site.
Black site?
Run by who?
Yeah, I don't know.
Somebody with tech,
somebody with deep pockets.
Maybe Russians?
Chinese, maybe.
Well, this ain't Chinese.
It says our names.
Our unit designations.
How do you know that?
I don't know.
I just do.
Fuck me.
What?
Mags are all topped off.
Mine too.
Same.
Why would somebody do that?
Better yet,
who the fuck would do it?
Yeah.
What's the last
thing you remember?
Hasakah.
Gunfight.
Donnie.
And that huge siren blast.
And that electric shock.
Felt like a damn taser on roids.
That's a fucking understatement.
And then just...
just nightmares.
- We gotta move.
- Go where?
Whoever did this to us
put us here.
They did it for a reason.
They'll be back.
The sooner the better.
Yeah, I'm with you, boss.
Say we get out of
here right now.
Heads on a swivel.
Let's move.
[unsettling music]
Go on.
What are you doing?
I don't know. I just...
felt like that's what
I was supposed to do.
Now what?
Try manual.
[unsettling music]
[grunts]
Jax!
[music intensifying]
Okay, on me.
Together.
[both grunting]
- Got it?
- Yep.
One...
two...
three...
[grunts]
Easy!
Wants to close.
- Got it?
- Yeah. We got it.
Reyes?
[creaking]
Give me...
[grunts]
[loud whoosh, bang]
[laughs]
Got him, buddy, eh?
Careful, that'll cut
your ass in half.
- Shit.
- Give me one.
Move it.
[unsettling music]
This one's fucked.
Look. It's bent.
Warped off its track.
[unsettling music]
[creaking]
[eerie music]
Reyes.
You're up.
Let's go to comms.
Shit.
[unsettling music]
I'm at a junction.
I can go up, down
into darkness.
Or I've got a little light
just ahead.
Is that the other
side of this wall?
[Reyes] Think so.
All right, we'll check it out.
Be careful.
I'll do that.
[unsettling music]
[creaking]
[clank]
[unsettling music]
Yeah. I'm through.
I'm on the other
side of your hatch.
I'm in a passageway, kind of
like the one that you're in.
Just a little bit longer.
How much longer?
[Reyes]
20, maybe 25 yards.
There's an intersection.
And it T's left and right.
[Reyes] [breathing heavily]
[unsettling music]
Thanks, dude.
- You good?
- Yeah.
Hey, boss?
Take a look at this.
Hey, check out
these gnarly-ass burns.
The impact marks.
Like someone was trying
pretty fucking hard
to get in here.
Hey.
This place is like one big maze.
Have you ever seen
anything like this?
No. Never.
[Rhodie]
It's got to be underground.
[Nash] More underwater.
Yeah.
I've heard of places like this.
Big old massive
prisons underwater.
They keep spooks, HVTs,
you know, stuff like that.
Team buddy of mine,
he said he synced it.
Said they were calling it
the North Atlantic Vault
or something like that.
Said it was a huge
underwater prison.
- Bullshit.
- No.
I swear to God he
told me he synced it,
and I believe him.
That would explain the airlock.
[distant scream]
What the hell was that?
Come on.
Wait, we're going
to go towards it?
[tense music]
[whirring, clicking]
What is it?
[tense music]
Are you good?
[low rumbling]
[deep, pulsating noise]
[beeping]
[tense music]
What's with the clamp?
[static]
Power failure.
This place must be dying.
Hey, on me.
[tense music]
[static]
Fuck me.
[dramatic sting]
Oh, shit.
Holy shit, man.
Hold it!
Hold the room.
Reyes, Gibbs, on me.
Nash.
[unsettling music]
[music intensifying]
[speaking Russian
frantically]
[whispers] Sh, sh, sh, sh.
Hey. It's okay. It's okay.
- [speaking Russian]
- [Kelly] Got you. Got you.
[speaking Russian]
[chains clanking]
Pull the lever.
Pull the lever,
the last lever.
Pull it, pull it, pull it.
[clanking]
[bang, thud]
[tense music]
[grunts]
[Kelly] Come on, now.
Come on.
[squishy footsteps]
[loud rumbling]
[creature growling]
[creature roaring]
[screams]
[creature growling]
[gunfire]
[action music]
[grunting, gasps]
[creature growling]
[action music]
[gunfire]
[creature growling]
[gun beeping]
[gun powers up]
Holy shit!
[unsettling music]
The hell is that thing?
[creature growling]
[rapid gunfire]
[squishing]
[speaking Russian]
Hey, wait!
Come on.
Well, who the hell is she?
Where's Gibbs?
Fuck.
[speaking Russian]
[creature growling]
[squishy stomping]
[creature roaring]
[dramatic music]
Kelly...
Run.
Fucking run!
[gunfire]
[action music]
[creature roaring]
[gunfire]
Come on!
Let's find a way out!
Hey, give me cover!
Down, down, down!
[gunfire]
[action music]
[speaking Russian]
[Kelly] Hey, find a way out!
And watch her.
Like she's one of my own!
That ain't gonna hold.
You gotta be kidding me, man.
Come on!
Way out, on me.
[action music]
[creature roaring]
[banging]
Go, go, go.
Go! I'm right behind you!
[banging]
Go.
Go, you go.
[action music]
[banging]
[creature roaring]
Reyes, let's go!
[gunfire]
[creature roaring]
[action music]
[banging]
[creature growling]
Hey!
[gunfire]
[Rhodie] Reyes!
[creature roaring]
[crawling]
[clanking]
- [Russian Girl grunting]
- Clear!
[Russian Girl grunting]
[speaking Russian]
I'm just trying to help.
Come on.
Got you.
Fuck!
- Take my weapon.
- I got you.
Come on.
[panting]
Where's Reyes?
[Nash] Fuck. That's my fucking
brother, dude.
Look, I only believe
in two things.
Jesus Christ and Dolly Parton.
And those things don't look
like the Messiah nor the Queen.
So can we all please agree
that those are fucking aliens?!
Hey! Enough!
How did you know
how to use that thing?
[Russian Girl]
[speaking Russian]
She says we ain't gonna make it.
Appreciate that, darling.
That's real kind of you.
Fuck!
How is she?
Grazed her. Just hit me.
Cauterized the wound.
[speaking Russian]
- What's she say?
- She said she's fine.
We need to go.
Didn't know you spoke Russian.
Yeah, me neither.
Who are you?
[speaking Russian]
What?
She called us sleepers.
Said she ain't telling us shit.
Hey.
We just saved
your ass from those things.
What are they?
[speaking Russian]
Huh? What?
She said you already told us.
I knew it!
It was aliens!
It was fucking aliens!
I knew the whole time!
God almighty, I told ya!
Okay.
Okay, so...
So where the hell are we?
[speaking Russian]
Kelly.
She said we're on this ship.
A ship?
[Rhodie] Fuck.
Like a spaceship?
A spaceship?!
What is happening here, guys?
Am I fucking...
Okay. All right. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
All good.
We need to go.
They will be coming for us.
She speaks English.
Hey. Go where?
A safe place.
A safe place?
On a spaceship?!
- [Kelly & Rhodie] Nash!
- Not another fuckin' word.
Guys, I'm sorry.
But we just lost
two more brothers,
and I don't want to lose
any more of them, all right?
I'm just having a really
hard time with this right now.
Yeah, we all are.
But hearing you piss
down your leg ain't helping.
I'm sorry.
God. What are we gonna do?
I don't fucking know.
But I know my little girl
ain't gonna grow up
with me being
a picture on the wall.
Uh, hang on, boss.
I don't mean any disrespect.
I'm just gonna say
one more thing, okay?
But it sounds like
you're saying that
we should take over the ship
and just fly our
asses back to Earth, right?
Okay? Okay.
I'm with it. I'm with it.
We'll go with it.
But one of those things almost
wiped out our entire team.
So what do we do?
We find the one nice one,
the one that they give
goop-filled
jelly donuts to,
and we ask him,
hey, pal, do me a favor.
Will you fly me
back to Tennessee?
'Cause I got some moonshine
buried in my backyard--
Shut the fuck up.
And calm the fuck down.
Hey!
We must keep moving.
Then get out of the way.
[nightmarish music]
[creature growling]
[music intensifying]
[nightmarish music]
[gunshot]
[blast]
[creature growling]
[nightmarish music]
[man screaming]
[creature growling]
[creature roaring]
[nightmarish music]
[creature growling]
Bro, what are we doing?
How do we know
she's on our side?
Well, she's been running
from them things
just as fast as we were.
Yeah, but, I mean, what if...
Kelly's got this.
Just gotta trust her, man.
If you say so.
It's okay. It's okay.
Cover. Cover.
It's okay.
Give me your name.
Tell me your name.
Ravshana.
Ravi.
Okay, Ravi. I'm Kelly.
The big one with the scars.
Is that the leader?
Yes.
How many has it got?
One is too many.
Dozens?
More.
As big as this place is,
it's not gonna be
easy to find us.
No, they'll know where we are.
They have motion sensors.
[whispers] Yo. Yo.
Fuck you doin'?
I got your shit.
What are they after?
A meal.
They're hungry.
Wait, what?
She's kidding, right?
I mean, she...
She's gotta be pulling our leg.
[unsettling music]
[creature growling]
[squishy stomping]
[soft static, zapping]
[unsettling music]
What's inside it?
Can't tell.
Glass is all scratched up.
Way too cloudy to see
anything.
[spits]
[splat]
[unsettling music]
[pulsating]
[whirring]
[beeping]
Hold.
[unsettling music]
[dramatic sting]
- [growling]
- What? What is it?
That's a fucking person.
Sleepers.
[unnerving music]
[pulsating]
God almighty, this is all
sorts of fucked up, man.
We shouldn't be here.
We need to go now.
Yeah. Yeah, I'm with her.
We need to get
the fuck out of here.
[unsettling music]
Jax, seeing as you're
my best friend and all,
I'd like to share
something with you.
Shit, what now, bruh?
You've been tripping
since we've been abducted.
That's just it.
I've been thinking about it.
I don't think we were abducted.
I think we were raptured.
- Raptured?
- Yeah.
What, this look like
heaven to you?
This ain't heaven or hell.
This is the book of Revelation,
brother, and we're living it.
And I don't think
those are aliens.
Those are demons.
What do you think?
I think your daddy should
have thought twice before
he started banging his sister.
- Jax.
- Yo.
[Kelly] Bandage.
Thank you.
For what?
[Ravi] Helping me.
I'm sorry for your friends.
Me too.
Where are you from?
Here.
Originally.
My family was from
a place called Sochi.
You know Sochi?
Black Sea?
Have you been there?
I haven't.
But I heard it's beautiful.
What about you?
New York.
- [Ravi] America.
- Yeah.
Land of the free.
Home of the brave.
That's been the plan.
What's your daughter's name?
Sara.
[Ravi]
What about her mother?
She lives with her.
And the two of you?
This ain't the job
for most wives.
Have you always been a soldier?
Pretty much.
[Ravi] What is it you like
so much about it?
[sighs] Like?
Is it the fighting
for something,
or simply the fighting?
[somber music]
[zapping]
[tense music]
What's all this?
Anything and everything
they thought
could be worth taking back.
[tense music]
[clicking]
Relax.
You'll hear them
before you see them.
[tense, pulsating music]
Kelly.
Yeah?
I've been thinking.
About what?
They know where we are.
They know where we're headed.
It's only a matter of time
before they get ahead of us
and try and box us in.
That's what I'd do.
Yeah.
What?
We'll make a stand.
No, you can't fight
them straight on.
You have to hit and run.
We need some bait.
Fuck that.
Relax, bro.
I'll do it.
You sure about that?
I run a 4.5 with gear.
Any of y'all could beat that?
I got you, boss.
Come on, bro, like--
That should be all right.
All right?
Good.
I got it.
Just be ready.
[loud rumbling]
[sinister music]
[creature growling]
[zapping, sparking]
[dramatic music]
[creature roaring]
♪ Mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm ♪
♪ California knows how
to party ♪
[creature roaring]
♪ California knows how
to party ♪
♪ In the city,
city of LA ♪
[overwhelming music]
♪ In the city,
good ol' Watts ♪
♪ In the city... ♪
[creature growling]
♪ We keep it rockin'
We keep it rockin' ♪
[gunfire]
Come on, motherfucker!
Come get some!
Come on!
[creature growling]
[overwhelming music]
[shouting]
[gunfire]
[overwhelming music]
♪ In the city... ♪
Come on, let's go!
Let's go!
[grinding, churning music]
[gunfire]
♪ In the city... ♪
- Clear!
- Comin' in!
[squishing]
All right, I'll admit it.
I like her.
Too easy.
Nah.
That right there is what
we call our Zip-a-Mall focus.
Did you guys see Scars?
Negative.
Nah.
They don't work like that.
Their leaders are never bait.
[tense music]
[banging]
Shit.
[shouting]
[gunfire]
Shit.
[shouting]
[action music]
[gunfire]
Move, move, move!
[action music]
- Jax, move!
- Come on! Come on!
Aah!
[shouts]
- Let's go! Let's go!
- Aah!
[screams]
Let's go! Go, go!
[action music]
[shouts]
[gunfire]
[indistinct]
Oh, hell, no!
[shouting]
[gunfire]
[action music]
[coughs]
I got you.
I got you, Kelly.
[coughing]
It smells so bad.
[Ravi] [whimpering]
[Nash] [indistinct]
It's like...
It's like standing in popcorn.
It's people!
It's fucking people!
Holy shit!
- Shut the fuck up!
- [Nash screams]
- This is insane!
- [Kelly] Everybody shut up!
[Anya] That is good advice.
[unsettling music]
Mama?
Ravi!
Mama!
[splash]
Come.
Mama? Mama?
[speaking Russian]
[zapping, sparking]
Who are you?
Russian fourth guards?
You talk too much.
[Anya] Come!
[zapping, sparking]
[tense music]
What about the sensors?
Stay close.
Only go where I go.
[tense music]
Ravi, show them.
Nash.
Rhodie.
[tense music]
[creaking, clang]
5[tense music]
[speaking Russian]
What's a Russian tank
commander doing here?
For the same reasons
special forces are.
How long have you been awake?
I don't know, a few hours.
Hours?
[speaking Russian]
We were ambushed.
Constantine was
carrying the charges.
He sacrificed himself to
give us a chance to escape.
Tell me, where did you wake up?
I don't know.
A room about this size.
Our names stenciled
below our pods.
Our weapons and kit packed
conveniently with us.
Not conveniently.
Purposely.
It was a trophy room.
Congratulations.
You're souvenirs.
How long have you been awake?
I can't know for sure.
20, 30 years.
How old do you think she is?
Did she just say 20 or 30 years?
[Anya] That's right.
You can't be serious.
It's very hard to
track time in here.
She was born after the fall.
Fall?
The invasion.
Invasion?
It's our own fault, really.
We were the ones who
rang the dinner bell.
What the hell is
she talking about?
In '77, your NASA
sent out a probe.
It had a map stamped on it,
telling whoever found it
exactly where we were.
Admittedly, there were those
who were opposed to
the inclusion of the map.
They called it
the Stamp of Osiris,
after the Egyptian god of death.
Okay, tell us more
about the invasion.
I am only a trophy, like you.
I only know what I've been
able to piece together.
But the war...
It's over.
They crushed Earth
in a matter of weeks.
With all the intel
we gave them, it was easy.
What intel?
They collected us first.
The world's greatest
military strategists on air,
land, and sea.
They have a device
which allows them
to hardwire into us.
You...
You had nightmares? Yes?
They were not nightmares.
They were war games.
War games to study exactly
how we would fight
and how we could be defeated.
And the strange impulses
you cannot explain.
The gifts you woke up with,
where do you think
they came from?
The connection they
made went two ways.
Accidental transfer.
Spillover.
And the ship?
It's basically
a giant shipping freighter
bringing home the spoils of war.
What spoils?
What they came here for.
Livestock.
Their cargo hold.
With all those pods.
Deck 31.
Yes. That entire hold failed
after the uprising.
Ravi's father was with
another group that got loose.
Sabotaged the reactor.
Wait, what does that mean?
Where are we?
I have no idea.
Floating in space?
[Ravi]
She's telling the truth.
We don't share with sleepers.
It's how we've stayed alive
as long as we have.
They find you, you will talk
and lead them back to us.
So why share with us now?
I have no choice.
With my team gone,
I need you to help finish.
Finish what?
They are attempting to repair
their communications relay.
[Kelly]
And how do you know this?
My gift.
I can hear them.
You can understand those things.
They are almost
ready to broadcast.
If the transmission goes out,
their friends will
know where we are.
They will come.
They will wipe us out
and harvest the remaining holds.
We must stop them.
[unsettling music]
I can't believe this is it.
It's how I go out.
We're never going home.
How are you holding up?
I just realized
that if she's still alive...
...she's, like, 40 years old.
Yeah.
I was thinking the same thing
about Beth and the boys.
You know what
I keep thinking about?
I can't get out of my mind?
Cargo hold.
All those people just getting
sucked up into an alien ship.
Wake up and then served on
a platter for evening chow.
So what are we going to do?
[Kelly] You know
where the comm center is?
I do.
Top deck.
It's their base,
where they're strongest.
What's the plan?
From what Ravi has told me,
there can be no more
than two dozen left.
Why don't we just take
the fight to them?
Too risky.
Too many.
Got it.
[Anya] We will use
the ventilation shafts.
But once we enter,
they will be on us in seconds.
Unless they have something
else to keep them busy.
You have what
you need to take it out?
Okay.
Lead the way.
[unsettling music]
[grunting]
It really hurts.
This harness is
pinching my bean bag.
What do they use these for?
For air?
There's no way those big fuckers
crawl through this thing.
[unsettling music]
Shit.
The comms center is right there.
We will repel in,
plant the charges,
and hopefully make it back to
the bulkhead before detonation.
That's where we come in.
All right, I'm counting on you
to keep them safe.
You got it, boss.
I can't wait.
We'll keep them busy,
hold them off as long as we can.
Press here and here
to activate the shield.
Here and here to turn it off.
Anya.
Anya Mitov.
Michael Kelly.
Good luck.
Watch your ass, big man.
Hey, you too, hillbilly.
All right, let's move.
[tense music]
[creatures growling]
[zapping, sparking]
[Kelly] Come here.
[tense music]
That's it?
[whispers] That's it?
[creatures growling]
We wait.
[sighs]
[unsettling music]
[low, pulsating sound]
[beeping]
[creature growling]
Here we are.
[creature roaring]
[Kelly] Here we are,
motherfucker, come and get us.
[tense music]
I liked Jax.
He was nice.
Yeah, he's the coolest.
So, uh...
Who's Constantine?
He was my best friend.
Yeah, I bet he's
pretty cool, too, huh?
I'm sorry about that.
Me, too.
[creature growling]
He's moving.
[tense music]
[music intensifying]
[creature growling]
[dramatic sting]
[squishy footsteps]
[creature growling]
[creature roaring]
[creatures growling]
[creature growling]
[creature screeches]
[gunfire]
[unnerving music]
[creature roaring]
[gunfire]
[tense music]
[music intensifying]
[gunfire]
[action music]
[creature roaring]
[creature growling]
- What the fuck?
- The hell they going?
[creature roaring]
[gunfire]
[rattling]
They're coming.
[Kelly] Nash, you copy?
Over.
[Nash] Roger that. Over.
Tangos inbound.
Get the fuck out of there.
[gunfire]
Get out right now!
Fuck me.
[gunfire]
[Kelly] Rhodie, they're fucked.
Not if you can get to them.
Rhodie!
[gunfire]
Nash, I'm coming to you!
By hook or by crook.
[gunfire]
[dramatic music]
[creature screeches]
[creature growling]
[tense music]
Fuck you.
[blast]
[gunshot, squish]
[gunfire]
[tense music]
Ravi. Go.
Go! Go!
[gunfire]
Go!
Now you.
Go with her.
Keep her alive.
[gunfire]
[dramatic music]
Mama, stop!
Here it comes...
[gunfire]
Mama!
[creature growling]
[gunfire]
Mama!
[creature roaring]
Come on.
Come on, come on.
Mama!
[creatures growling]
[beeping]
[blasts]
Nash, you copy?
Nash!
It's done!
It's fucking done!
But I got a heap of trouble
in tow!
Hang tight.
I'm coming to you.
[zapping, sparking]
Shit!
[Nash] Go right! Go right!
Come on! They're coming!
Yeah, yeah, I know.
Hey, hang on. Hang on.
Get in.
- What?
- Get in!
All right. Good.
Wait. What are you doing?
Whatever I can, sweetheart.
Whatever I can.
Let's go!
Let's do some country-ass shit!
Come and get me,
you big, ugly motherfucker!
[banging]
[screaming] Yeahhh!
[creatures running]
[tense music]
[Nash] Come on!
If you can hear me, boss,
it's been real.
[tense music]
♪ In the city,
good ol' Watts ♪
[gunfire]
♪ In the city,
city of Compton ♪
[gunfire]
♪ We keep it rockin'
We keep it rockin' ♪
Oh, fuck.
Fuck.
Okay, okay, all right.
♪ We keep it rockin' ♪
[buzzer blaring]
[creatures running]
Nah.
[gunfire]
[metal scraping]
[clang]
[unsettling music]
[creature growling]
[creature roaring]
[unsettling music]
[man speaking French]
[crowd speaking French
at once]
[voices become more frantic]
[birds chirping]
[tense, but tender music]
[wind rustling leaves]
[whirring]
[clanging]
[loud rumbling]
Sara!
[frantic male voice]
[speaking French]
Please, please...
[Ravi] Kelly?
- Kelly, are you all right?
- Yeah.
Nash?
And your mother?
[creatures growling]
[creature roaring]
[intensifying music]
[overwhelming music]
[creature growling]
[creature roaring]
[overwhelming music]
Whiny bitch.
[creature growling]
[laughs]
How's it hangin', boss?
Get me the fuck down!
All right, hang tight.
[laughs]
I'm on it.
- Where we going, boss?
- To find Ravi.
[gunshot]
Here.
[tense music]
[gunfire]
Give me that.
Hold the door.
- Ravi!
- I'm here!
Back away!
Get away! Get away!
[Nash] We got company!
[gunfire]
God almighty!
[Man] [speaking French]
[gunfire]
[creature roaring]
Ravi! Ravi!
[gunfire]
Hey! Are you okay?
Okay, go.
[indistinct]
[gunfire]
Let's move! Let's move!
[action music]
Go! Move over! Move over!
Go, go, go!
[action music]
[gunfire]
[creature roaring]
Nash!
[gunfire]
I'm out!
[music intensifying]
[gunfire]
[blast]
[unsettling, pulsating music]
[drops gun]
Boom! [laughs]
We did it.
We fucking did it.
Fuck.
[dramatic sting]
[sinister music]
[creature growling]
[squishy footsteps]
[creature roaring]
Go!
Come on.
Come on, motherfucker.
[creature growling]
Come on!
Come on! Come on!
[creature growling]
[blades clanging]
[dramatic music]
[shouts]
[creature roaring]
No!
[groans]
[dramatic music]
[creature roaring]
[sinister music]
[creature growling]
[screams, moans]
[dramatic music]
[creature growling]
You want me?
I'm right here!
[creature roaring]
[splat]
[blood pouring]
[Kelly panting]
[tense music]
[music intensifying]
[clanking]
[tense music]
[dramatic music]
[unsettling music]
[woman vocalizing]
[ethereal, soothing music]
[action music]
[music softens]
[unsettling music]